Samuel Dash Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Organizations and Committees, 1764-2003 (Box 105-179)
  - Georgetown University Law Center, Institute of Criminal Law and Procedure, Washington, D.C. See also Containers 165-173, Judicial Conference of the District of Columbia Circuit, Committee on Laws Pertaining to Mental Disorders; and Container 173, Legal Aid Agency of the District of Columbia
    - Projects and proposals
      - Defendant pre-arraignment, 1966-1968
      - District of Columbia Court Study Program, 1967-1968
      - District of Columbia Office of Criminal Justice Planning
        - 1968
        - 1969, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 155)
        - 1970
      - Drug addict treatment center, 1966-1967
      - Employment discrimination clinic, undated
      - Eyewitness identification, 1971-1977, undated
      - Forensic science
        - 1966-1972, 1979, (4 folders)
        - 1980-1981, undated, (4 folders) (Box 156)
      - Improving Evidence Gathering through a Computer-Assisted Intake Program, 1986-1987
      - Law, juvenile processes and mental disorders, 1966
      - Magistrate and United States Commissioner Systems, 1966
      - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, correction and administration of criminal justice, 1968
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1965-1972, (2 folders)
        - 1977, undated (Box 157)
      - Offender rehabilitation, 1966-1969, undated, (3 folders)
      - Plea bargaining in the United States
        - 1974-1978
        - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 158)
      - Police-prosecutor relations, 1987
      - Police studies, 1967-1968, (3 folders)
      - Precinct representation in the District of Columbia, 1967
      - Preliminary hearing
        - General, 1966-1967, undated
        - “Preliminary Hearing in the District of Columbia,” undated (Box 159)
      - Pretrial clinic, 1966-1971, undated, (2 folders)
      - Preventive detention, 1971-1972, undated
      - Prior crime surveys (Box 160)
        - Cleveland, Ohio, 1966, (2 folders)
        - Illinois, 1968, (2 folders)
        - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967
        - New Haven, Conn., undated
      - Prisoner work release, 1971
      - Released prisoners who do not return to prison, undated
      - Role of local law enforcement in controlling illegal immigration and other transitional crime, 1995
      - Role of prison industries now and in the future, 1975
      - Space age teleforensics, 1986, 1996-1998, undated (Box 161)
      - Stop and frisk, 1970-1971, undated
      - Victim impact statements, 1986
      - Vocational rehabilitation, 1966-1967
    - Reports
      - Annual,1967-1973
      - Monthly, 1966
      - Periodic, 1968-1969, 1977, undated
    - Research fellowships, 1968-1969
    - U.S. Advisory Committee on Human Rights of the Marangopoulos Foundation, 1986-1989, undated, (4 folders) (Box 162)
  - Harvard Defenders, 1989, 1995-2000
  - International League for Human Rights
    - “Bloody Sunday” Inquiry See also Containers 246-252, Justice Denied: A Challenge to Lord Widgery's Report on “Bloody Sunday”
      - Correspondence and newspaper clippings
        - 1991, 1997-1998, (4 folders)
        - 1999-2000, (6 folders) (Box 163)
        - 2001, (1 folder) (Box 164)
        - 2002-2003, undated
      - Paramount Classics movie, 2001-2002
    - Chile Eight, 1982
    - Miscellany, 1972, 1985, 1992, 1998-2002
    - Northern Ireland, 1975-1977, 1996-2003, undated
    - Trip to Soviet Union
      - Business cards, notebook, and notes, 1972
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973, (3 folders)
      - Expense reports and invoices, 1972
      - List of attendees, 1972
      - List of those receiving Dash's speech, 1972
      - Speech, 1972
  - Judicial Conference of the District of Columbia Circuit, Committee on Laws Pertaining to Mental Disorders See also Containers 152-162, Georgetown University Law Center, Institute of Criminal Law and Procedure, Washington, D.C.; and Container 173, Legal Aid Agency of the District of Columbia (Box 165)
    - Act for Residential Care of the Mentally Retarded, 1967-1968
    - Chronological file
      - Correspondence
        - 1965-1968, (6 folders)
        - 1969-1973, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 166)
      - Memoranda
        - 1965-1966, (6 folders)
        - 1967-1971, (7 folders) (Box 167)
    - Final report, 1970, (3 folders) (Box 168)
    - Financial statements, 1968-1969 (Box 169)
    - General, 1965-1969, undated, (2 folders)
    - Project on Community Mental Health Services and the Law, Study of Area C Community Mental Health Center
      - General
        - 1966-1967, (5 folders)
        - 1968-1970, undated (Box 170)
      - Reports, 1969
    - Project on Law, Mental Disorders and the Juvenile Process
      - Budget requests and grant applications, 1967-1970, undated, (3 folders)
      - Disposition of mentally disordered juvenile delinquents, questionnaire and encoding instructions, undated
      - Financial records
        - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967
        - Office equipment, supplies, and other disbursements, 1969-1971, undated
        - Statements, 1967-1971 (Box 171)
      - Juvenile court study, 1970, undated
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Personnel records, 1967-1971
      - Reports and studies, 1967-1969, (4 folders)
    - Project on Laws Applicable in the District of Columbia Pertaining to Mental Disorders (Box 172)
      - Subproject on Children Suffering from Mental Disorders, Preventive Aspects, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
      - Subproject on Vocational Rehabilitation of Mentally Disordered Offenders
        - General, 1966
        - Reports
          - 1966, (2 folders)
          - 1967 (Box 173)
  - Legal Aid Agency for the District of Columbia See also Containers 152-162, Georgetown University Law Center, Institute of Criminal Law and Procedure, Washington, D.C.; and Containers 165-172, Judicial Conference of the District of Columbia Circuit, Committee on Laws Pertaining to Mental Disorders
    - General, 1967-1977, undated, (4 folders)
    - Notes, 1967, undated
    - Printed matter, 1974
  - Montgomery County Democratic Central Committee, Md., Task Force on Administration of Justice, 1971-1973
  - National Association of Attorneys General (Box 174)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1972, 1986, (4 folders)
    - Printed matter
      - 1971-1977, (3 folders)
      - 1986 (Box 175)
  - National Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers See same container, National Association of Defense Lawyers in Criminal Cases
  - National Association of Defense Lawyers in Criminal Cases
    - Annual convention, 1967
    - Correspondence, 1961, 1971-1981, 1988-1996
    - Membership lists, 1961-1969
    - Printed matter, 1961-1965, 1994, undated
  - Philadelphia Council for Community Advancement, Philadelphia, Pa.,1964-1965
  - Public Defender Service for the District of Columbia See Container 173, Legal Aid Agency for the District of Columbia
  - Sunshine Mining Co. (Box 176)
    - Board meetings, 1979-1981, undated, (7 folders)
    - Clippings and press releases
      - 1979
      - 1980, undated, (2 folders) (Box 177)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980
    - Financial records, 1980-1986
    - Legal documents, 1979-1981, (4 folders)
    - Notes, undated
    - Silver certificates, 1980, (2 folders) (Box 178)
  - Supreme and Superior Courts of Pennsylvania, Criminal Procedural Rules Committee, 1961-1962, (2 folders)
  - United Nations Conference to Consider Amendments to the Single Convention on Narcotic Drugs of 1961, 1972
  - United Way of the National Capital Area, Code of Ethics Subcommittee
    - 1764, 2001-2002, (3 folders)
    - Undated (Box 179)
  - Voluntary Committee of Lawyers, 1996-1998
  - Washington Council of Lawyers, Washington, D.C., Special Committee on Iran Contra and Watergate Reform, 1981-1992, (7 folders)
- Teaching File, 1925-2003 (Box 180-201)
  Course outlines, syllabi, lecture notes, exam questions, surveys, printed matter, articles, clippings, and correspondence.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of course and therein by type of material.
  - Bill of Rights and the Prosecution of Crime, 1986, summer (Box 180)
  - Class Actions and Mass Torts, 1977-1979, 1987-1991, undated
    - Cases and papers
    - Notebook, (3 folders)
  - Criminal Justice
    - Classes
      - 1967, fall
        - Class list and syllabus
        - Lecture notes
      - 1968, spring
      - 1969
        - Spring
          - Class lists
          - Lecture notes and miscellaneous course material
        - Fall
      - 1969-1970 (Box 181)
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellaneous course material
      - 1970, fall
      - 1970-1971, lecture notes
      - 1971
        - Spring
          - Class lists
          - Lecture notes, (2 folders)
        - Fall
          - Class lists
          - Lecture notes and miscellaneous course material
      - 1972, fall
      - 1973, spring
        - Class list
        - Lecture notes
      - 1975 (Box 182)
        - Spring
          - Class lists
          - Lecture notes
        - Fall
      - 1978, fall
        - Exam and critique
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellany
        - Syllabus
      - 1980
        - Spring
          - Exam and critique
          - Lecture notes, (2 folders)
          - Miscellaneous course material
        - Fall
          - Class list
          - Lecture notes
          - Miscellaneous course material (Box 183)
          - Syllabus
      - 1982, spring
        - Miscellaneous course material
        - Syllabus
      - 1984, spring
      - 1986
        - Spring
        - Fall
      - 1987, spring
      - 1988, spring
      - 1989
        - Spring
        - Fall
      - 1990, spring
      - 1991, spring
      - 1992, fall
      - 1993, spring
      - 1994, spring
        - Class list and exam
        - Lecture notes
      - 1995, spring (Box 184)
        - Lecture notes
        - Syllabus
      - 1996, spring
        - Class lists, exam, and syllabus
        - Lecture notes
        - Professor-course survey questionnaire
      - 1997, spring
      - 1998, spring
        - Exam and syllabus
        - Lecture notes, (3 folders)
        - Miscellaneous course material (Box 185)
        - Professor-course survey questionnaire
      - 2000, spring
      - 2001
        - Spring
          - Class lists
          - Exam
          - Lecture notes, (2 folders)
          - Professor-course survey questionnaire
        - Fall
      - 2002, spring (Box 186)
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellaneous course material, (2 folders)
        - Professor-course survey questionnaire
        - Syllabus
      - 2003, spring
        - Class lists
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellaneous course material and syllabus
      - Undated
    - Supplemental material
      - 1925, 1967
      - 1971-1992, (6 folders) (Box 187)
      - 1995, undated (Box 188)
  - Criminal Law
    - 1966, fall
    - 1989
      - Spring
      - Fall
        - Lecture notes, (5 folders)
        - Syllabus
    - 1996, fall, lecture notes, (3 folders) (Box 189)
    - 1998, fall
      - Class lists and syllabus
      - Lecture notes, (5 folders)
  - Criminal Procedure
    - Classes
      - 1978, spring
        - Exam
        - Lecture notes
      - 1985, spring
    - Supplemental material, undated (Box 190)
  - Legislative Investigation Seminar
    - Classes
      - 1987, fall
      - 1988
        - Spring
        - Fall
      - 1989, fall
      - 1991, fall
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellaneous course material and syllabus
        - Paper topics
      - 1992, fall
      - 1993, fall
      - 1994, fall
        - Class lists and syllabus
        - Miscellaneous course material and paper topics
      - 1995, fall
        - Class lists and syllabus
        - Miscellaneous course material, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 191)
        - Notes and problems
        - Paper topics
      - 1996, fall
      - 1997, fall
        - Class lists and syllabus
        - Lecture notes and miscellaneous course material
        - Paper topics
      - 1998, fall
      - 2000, fall
      - 2001, fall
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellaneous course material, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 192)
        - Paper topics and syllabus
        - Professor-course survey questionnaire
      - 2002, fall
        - Lecture notes and miscellaneous course material
        - Paper topics and syllabus
        - Professor-course survey questionnaire
      - 2003, fall
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellaneous course material, (2 folders)
        - Syllabus
    - Miscellany, 1987-1994, undated
    - Reading material, 2001, (3 folders) (Box 193)
    - Subjects
      - Democratic National Committee Fund-raising
        - Exam problems, 1997, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany
          - 1996
          - 1997-1998, undated, (3 folders) (Box 194)
      - Enron Corp.
        - Chronologies, 1999-2002
        - Exam problems, 2002
        - Miscellany, 1999-2002, undated
        - Packets, 1999-2002, (2 folders)
      - Packwood, Bob (Box 195)
        - Appendices, 1995, undated
        - “A-C” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
        - General, 1988-1993, undated
        - Memorandum, 1993
      - Watergate Affair, 1973, undated
      - Whitewater Inquiry
        - Exam problems, 1991-1996
          - Nos. 1-2, (3 folders)
          - Nos. 3-6 (Box 196)
        - Miscellany, 1994-1998, undated, (4 folders)
    - Supplemental material
      - 1926, 1938, 1948
      - 1976-1991, (7 folders) (Box 197)
      - 1993-1997, undated, (3 folders) (Box 198)
  - Legal Writing Program, 1968-1971, undated
  - Miscellany, 1988-1990, 1997
  - Professional Responsibility
    - Classes
      - 1970, fall
      - 1972, fall
      - 1976, spring
      - 1979, spring (Box 199)
      - 1980, spring
        - Class list and syllabus
        - Lecture notes
      - 1983, fall
      - 1986, fall
      - 1987, fall
      - 1988, fall
      - 1991, fall
      - 1992
        - Spring
        - Fall
      - 1993
        - Spring
        - Fall
      - 1995, fall
        - Class lists and syllabus
        - Miscellaneous course material, (2 folders)
      - 2000, fall
      - 2001, fall (Box 200)
        - Class lists, exam, and syllabus
        - Professor-course survey questionnaire
      - 2002, fall
        - Class lists, exam, and syllabus
        - Lecture notes
        - Miscellaneous course material
        - Professor-course survey questionnaire
      - 2003, fall
      - Undated
    - Supplemental material
      - 1958, 1967-1975, 1984-1995, (3 folders)
      - 2001, undated (Box 201)
- General Correspondence, 1967-2003 (Box 201-206)
  Correspondence and memoranda.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1967-1972, (6 folders) (Box 201)
  - 1973, (1 folder) (Box 202)
  - 1974-1977, (5 folders)
  - 1978, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 203)
  - 1979, (3 folders)
  - 1980, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 204)
  - circa 1980-circa 1989
  - 1981-1986, (6 folders)
  - 1987-1990, (6 folders) (Box 205)
  - circa 1990-circa 1999
  - 1991-1994, (4 folders)
  - 1995-2003, undated, (10 folders) (Box 206)
- General Office File, 1895-2004 (Box 207-230)
  Correspondence, appointment calendars, biographical material, photographs, clippings, articles, printed matter, subject files, and receipts.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of person, organization, subject, or type of material and therein chronologically.
  - Admission to Maryland Bar, 1972 (Box 207)
  - American Law Institute Reporter, 1979-1983
  - Amnesty International, Centre for the Independence of Judges and Lawyers, 1978
  - Appointment calendars
    - 1963, 1977-1983, (6 folders)
    - 1984-1989, (6 folders) (Box 208)
    - 1990-1994, (5 folders) (Box 209)
  - Articles about Dash and mentions, 1968, 1977, 1985, 1992-1993, 1999, undated (Box 210)
  - Australian Institute of Criminology, 1979-1981
  - Biographical material, 1950, 1961, 1986-2004, undated
  - Caddy, Douglas, “Did Judge Sirica Cause the Watergate Cover-Up?” 1997
  - Capital punishment/death penalty, 1977-1982, 1993, undated
  - Chalizde, Valery
    - 1972, (2 folders)
    - 1973, undated (Box 211)
  - Christmas greetings, 1978
  - Christmas lists, 1978-1980, undated
  - Computer use in complex cases, 1976, undated
  - Conflict of interest, 1985-1989, 2002, undated
  - Corporate audit committees, 1977
  - Corporate ethics, 1977-1978, undated
  - Cosmos Club, Washington, D.C., 1988-2002
  - Criminal code, federal, 1978
  - Dash, Sara G. (wife), 1973-1977 (Box 212)
  - Dash family
    - Genealogy, 1983
    - Photographs, 1982, 1999, undated
  - Edbril, Donna E., circa 1979
  - Electronic surveillance, 1971, 1987-1988, 1997-2003, undated
  - Elman, Philip, “An Argument for Lowering Voices–Clinton's ’Private Moral Wrongs' and Starr's ’Torquemada Inquisition,'” 1998
  - Employment file
    - U.S. attorney, Philadelphia, Pa.
      - Correspondence and questionnaire, 1978
      - Newspaper clippings, 1978, (3 folders)
    - U.S. district judgeship, circa 1977
  - Expert legal testimony, 1984-1991
  - Foreign Assistance Act, 1976
  - Fourth European Conference of Law Faculties, Strasbourg, Austria, 1976 (Box 213)
  - Freedman, Monroe, attorney-client privilege, 1976
  - Georgetown University, Washington, D.C.
    - Academic Standards Committee, 1977-1983
    - Clerkship Committee, 1974-1975, 1998
    - Dean's Committee on Honorary Degrees, 1987, 2002
    - Faculty Affairs Committee
      - Appointments, 1992-1993
      - Rank and tenure
        - Carter, Barry E., 1986
        - Coffee, John C., Jr., 1978-1979, undated
        - Dash, Samuel, 1967-1968, undated
        - Edelman, Peter B., 1987-1988
        - Ernst, Daniel R., 1992-1993 (Box 214)
        - Gustafson, Charles H., 1976-1977
        - Miscellany, 1972-1976, 1986-1989, undated
        - Norton, Eleanor Holmes, 1988
        - Perdue, Wendy, 1988
        - Schwartz, Warren F., 1978-1979
        - Tague, Peter W.
          - General, 1979, undated, (2 folders)
          - Writings, 1974-1978, undated, (2 folders)
        - Tushnet, Mark, 1981
        - Weiss, Edith Brown, 1989
      - Self-study, 1978 (Box 215)
    - Judaic and Hebraic Studies, 1980-1982
    - Law Center
      - Activity reports of Dash, 1984-1995, 2001-2002
      - Budget Committee
        - Memoranda, 1968, 1979-1981
        - Statements, 1978-1982
      - Chair in Judaic Roots of American Law, 1976-1980
      - Committee on Professional Responsibility, 1985, 1991
      - Committee on Programs and Research, 1966-1969
      - Courses (Box 216)
        - Judaic Sources of American Law, 1981, 1987, (3 folders)
        - Schedules, 1982-1983
      - Faculty
        - Contract, 1972
        - Grievances, 1976, 1992-1998
      - Foreign visitors, 1968-1972, 1999-2002, undated
      - Institute for Criminal Law and Procedure See Containers 152-162, Georgetown University Law Center, Institute for Criminal Law and Procedure, Washington, D.C.
      - Law Club, 1974, undated
      - Law Library on International Law and Human Rights, 2000-2002
      - Memoranda
        - 1967, 1975-1985, (2 folders)
        - 1986-2004, undated, (5 folders) (Box 217)
    - Memoranda
      - 1969-1971, 1976-1987, (2 folders)
      - 1988-1985, 2002, undated (Box 218)
  - Goldhirsh, Reneé, 1983
  - Halperin, David, “Ethics Breakthrough or Ethics Breakdown? Kenneth Starr's Dual Roles as Private Practitioner and Public Prosecutor,” 2002
  - Insurance, 1978-1983, 1991-1995, undated
  - Israel, correspondence, 1964-1977, 1983, undated, (2 folders)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1974-1975
  - Jewish roots of the U.S. Constitution
    - Background information
      - General, 1920, circa 1950, 1957, 1962-1972, 1983-1987, undated
      - “Materials on the Jewish Legal Tradition,” 1976, (2 folders) (Box 219)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988, 1996
  - “Lawyers Role in the Adversary System,” 1967, (2 folders)
  - Letters of reference
    - 1969-1971, (3 folders)
    - 1972-1989, (9 folders) (Box 220)
    - 1990-2004, undated, (4 folders) (Box 221)
  - Meese, Edwin, III, independent counsel investigation, 1984-1985, (2 folders)
  - Michelson, Anatol, 1972-1973
  - Michigan and Ohio professional conduct and ethical rules, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 222)
  - Miscellany
    - Addresses, 1980, 1986-1992
    - Articles, 1970, 1977, 1986, 1996-2003, undated
    - Cases and guidelines, 1973-1981, 1989, 2002, undated
    - Fragments, undated
    - Notes, 1983-1988, 1995, undated
  - National Conference on Justice for All, 1980
  - Pretrial release and preventive detention (Box 223)
    - Articles, 1952-1956, 1966-1983, (6 folders)
    - Bail reform and codes in the District of Columbia, 1969, 1981 (Box 224)
    - Cases
      - Enhancement statutes, 1895, 1911, 1948-1982, (3 folders)
      - General
        - 1972-1981, (2 folders)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 225)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1971-1982
    - Notes, 1969-1981, undated
    - Printed matter
      - 1968, 1977-1980, (4 folders)
      - 1981, (1 folder) (Box 226)
  - Printed matter, 1963-1968, 1975, 1983, 1992, (5 folders)
  - Prosecutorial misconduct, 1984-1994, (2 folders) (Box 227)
  - Regan, Milton C., Jr., “Market Discourse and Moral Neutrality in Divorce Law,” undated
  - Reid, Chris, 1989
  - Requests for autographs, 1974-2003, undated, (3 folders)
  - Sentencing, 1971, undated
  - South Africa and Nelson Mandela
    - 1985
    - 1986-1998, undated, (5 folders) (Box 228)
  - Telephone number and address book, circa 1963-1971
  - Travel and expense receipts
    - 1965-1969
    - circa 1965-circa 1973 (Box 229)
    - 1970-1973, (4 folders)
  - Trip to Australia in 1992, 1977-1992, undated
  - United States Court of Appeals cases, 1974-1985
  - University of Washington School of Law Library, Seattle, Wash., and Washington Law Review, index to current legal periodicals, 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 230)
- Speech and Engagement File, 1961-2003 (Box 230-239)
  Correspondence, memoranda, speeches, printed matter, and newspaper clippings.
  Arranged chronologically by date of speech or engagement.
  - 1961, 1966-1970, (14 folders) (Box 230)
  - circa 1970-circa 1979
  - 1971-1975, (36 folders) (Box 231)
  - 1976-1980, (26 folders) (Box 232)
  - 1981
    - Apr., (2 folders) (Box 233)
    - May-Oct., (4 folders)
  - 1982-1983, (4 folders)
  - 1984
    - Mar., (2 folders) (Box 234)
    - May
    - No month
  - 1985-1987, (17 folders)
  - 1988-1989, (12 folders) (Box 235)
  - 1990-1992, (11 folders) (Box 236)
  - 1993
    - Feb.-Aug., (8 folders)
    - Oct. (Box 237)
    - No month, (2 folders)
  - 1994-1995, (18 folders)
  - 1996
    - Jan.-Mar., (2 folders)
    - Summer, (2 folders) (Box 238)
    - Nov.
  - 1997-1999, (22 folders)
  - 2000-2003, (18 folders) (Box 239)
  - Fragments, undated
- Writings File, 1748-2004 (Box 239-252)
  Articles, books, a play, and poems.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material and therein by title of work or chronologically.
  - Articles and book reviews (Box 239)
    - 1951-1978
    - 1980-2003, undated, (4 folders) (Box 240)
  - Books
    - Appellate Practice (manual), 1993
    - Chief Counsel: Inside the Ervin Committee–The Untold Story of Watergate, 1976
    - Eavesdroppers, 1971-1973
    - The Intruders: Unreasonable Searches and Seizures from King John to John Ashcroft (Box 241)
      - Correspondence, 1994-2003, undated
      - Drafts, 1994, 2001, undated, (2 folders)
      - Research material
        - Articles, press releases, and statements, 1950, 1997-2002, (3 folders)
        - Book excerpts
          - 1768, 1890, 1927, 1966-1973, (2 folders)
          - 1990-1999, undated, (3 folders) (Box 242)
        - Cases
          - Benanti v. United States, 1957
          - Bivens v. Six Unknown Named Agents, 1992-1994, undated
          - Boyd v. United States
            - Group 1, 1748-1885
            - Group 2, 1883-1891, 1930-1938
            - Group 3, 1982, 1989, 1995, undated (Box 243)
          - Bumper v. North Carolina, 1956, 1963-1968, 1994, undated, (2 folders)